[Music]
[Música]
upon arrival we speak with the blond,
al llegar se habla con el rubio
the recommended one, I have already
la recomendada ya lo
said in several places and various things and the
he dicho varios sitios y varias cosas y
same people get involved and say how about
lo mismo la gente se mete y dice que tal
another great one with his good things and his
otro grandes con sus cosas buenas y sus
bad things, aguayo hawai just like you think he
cosas malas aguayo hawai igual que crees
can fall better or worse, hey, but to
que puede caer mejor o peor oye pero
release 100,000 payments that you have earned
soltar 100.000 pagos que te has ganado
there at state Christmas although he had
ahí en navidad estatal aunque tenía
a lot of money towards me the payment for a
mucho dinero hacia mí el pago de un
new car from Sol Junio ​​and putting in the
coche nuevo de sol junio y echando las
hours that are his, I like those
horas que son suya me gusta entonces esa
respectable people in that sense and the
gente respetable en ese sentido y lo de
blond one is super respectable, I have already said
rubio un súper respetable yo ya he dicho
a sanctuary will be made, I get involved
se hará un santuario yo me meto
directly, okay, directly if I will have
directamente vale directamente si lo
given it at the moment but if not and how much, how much
habré dadas momento pero si no y cuánto
money is public, how much money does
cuánto dinero es público cuánto dinero
the blond generate,
género el rubio
well, 70,000 payments with 70 thousand to
pues 70.000 pagos con de 70 mil para
donate, how good man, I'll tell you one thing
donar qué bien tío que te digo una cosa
for a small association
para una asociación pequeña
five hundred euros, one thousand euros, they get them out of
quinientos euros mil euros les sacan de
[ __ ], I
la [__]
know one, I don't know if you saw the video, the one I
yo conozco uno no sé si viste el vídeo
made, they are from here, we go, I know him
el que hice son de aquí vamos lo conozco
because she is a friend of mine from the fence, we are
porque es una amiga mía desde el cerco
going to, she gets
le vamos a
very stressed many times because of
se agobia muchísimo muchas veces por
[ __ ] bills  maybe 100 bucks of
[__] facturas a lo mejor de 100 pavos
course they get up in the attic owing
claro es que se suben al desván debiendo
the vets and they have to
a los veterinarios y les tienen que ir
pay them in installments and such not only explain
pagando a plazos y tal no sólo explica
the new law is that there are many people for whom
al nuevo ley es que hay mucha gente que
500 euros is brutality for
quinientos euros es una brutalidad para
them and they are not going to solve anything for me
ellos y a mí no me van a resolver nada
because I have an expense of 17,000 euros
porque tengo un gasto de 17.000 euros
more or less a month I have to
más o menos al mes yo me lo tengo que
take out 3,500 euros one thousand euros 2008 or 270
sacar 3 500 euros mil euros 2008 o 270
thousand they are not going to solve it the
mil no me van a resolver al mes
following month I have the same [ __ ] but for
siguiente tengo la misma [__] pero a
these people it can solve their lives
esta gente les puede solucionar la vida
which means that you are helping a
que significa que estás ayudando un
lot of animals that will come from
montón de animales que van a venir de
behind those are the anonymous ones the
atrás esos son los anónimos los
important ones are the anonymous ones I go on
importantes son los anónimos yo salgo la
TV or I go on the internet I have my
tele o salgo en internet yo tengo mis
weapons it is but there are people who do not have
armas es pero hay gente que no tiene
weapons who are asking you please
armas que te lo está pidiendo por favor
help me in crime 120 euros to operate on
ayudarme en delito 120 euros para operar
this dog total that that
este perro de total
seems to me that those are
eso eso a mí me parece que eso son obras
important works they are very important works and the
importantes son obras muy importantes y
big ones do it that the
lo hacen los grandes eso lo hacen los
big ones do it because I do not give a [ __ ] thing I do
grandes porque yo no suelto un [__] yo
give money  On a personal level I go to
sí doy dinero a nivel particular voy a
two different places in Spain but I
dos diferentes sitios en españa pero yo
go to work to give it to others,
ponerme a trabajar para dárselo a otros
well no, I give my money what the
pues no yo le doy a mi dinero lo que la
night called is to take now yes it is
noche llamada es llevar ahora sí que es
true that it is to
verdad que
work we are at the end of the day it is to
es trabajar estamos al final del día es
work I mean they
trabajar es decir
have a lot of money yes but boy the one who has a
que tienen mucho dinero sí pero chico el
lot of money is because he does not give
que tiene mucho dinero es porque no da
the one who has a lot of money is because he does not
el que tiene mucho dinero es porque no
spend the rich are stingy by
gasta los ricos son tacaños por
nature so the one who gives is grateful for the
naturaleza pues el que da agradece lo lo
same that may suit them better or worse
mismo que les puede quedar mejor o peor
the blond may fall better or worse the
el rubio puede caer mejor o peor el
boy has also been given a job
chico lo han dado también una labor
could they could do it
podría podrían hacerlo
[Music]
[Música]